<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-01-29T12:53:41-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Hipcamp Engineering</title><subtitle>Hipcamp Engineering description
</subtitle><author><name>Bojan Babic</name></author><entry><title type="html">Bought the Deep Learning Book by Ian Goodfellow</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/ian-goodfellow-deep-learning-amazing-resource-for-neural-networks" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bought the Deep Learning Book by Ian Goodfellow" /><published>2020-01-21T22:16:01-08:00</published><updated>2020-01-21T22:16:01-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/ian-goodfellow-deep-learning-amazing-resource-for-neural-networks</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/ian-goodfellow-deep-learning-amazing-resource-for-neural-networks">&lt;p&gt;As I’m crunching through the Deep Learning course at Coursera, I’ve decided to broaden my Deep Learning knowledge. In the Coursera forum, people were mentioning this book at lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Deep-Learning-Adaptive-Computation-Machine/dp/0262035618&quot;&gt;Deep Learning&lt;/a&gt; is a comprehensive guide about Machine Learning and Deep Learning. It provides the math background regarding the main methodologies used in both. On the other hand, it provides the smooth transition from Machine Learning to Deep Learning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The book is essential for anyone who is deeply interested in this area. I’ve bought hardcover since I wanted to have this copy for my book collection.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Bojan Babic</name></author><category term="dnn" /><category term="deep learning" /><category term="deep neural networks" /><category term="ml" /><category term="machine learning" /><category term="coursera" /><category term="ian goodfellow" /><summary type="html">As I’m crunching through the Deep Learning course at Coursera, I’ve decided to broaden my Deep Learning knowledge. In the Coursera forum, people were mentioning this book at lot. Deep Learning is a comprehensive guide about Machine Learning and Deep Learning. It provides the math background regarding the main methodologies used in both. On the other hand, it provides the smooth transition from Machine Learning to Deep Learning. The book is essential for anyone who is deeply interested in this area. I’ve bought hardcover since I wanted to have this copy for my book collection.</summary></entry></feed>